 const ironmanQuiz = [
    
             {
            question: "Whats Tony Starks alter Ego",
            choice1: "Iron Man",
            choice2: "Thor",
            choice3: "Captain America",
            choice4: "hulk",
            answer: 1,
             },

         
            {
                question: "What is the name of the actor who plays Iron Man?",
                choice1: "Chris Evens",
                choice2: "Robert Downey Jr",
                choice3: "Happy Hogan",
                choice4: "Sandra ",
                answer: 2,
            },

            {
                question: "Who is Iron Man's MCU protegé?",
                choice1: "Antman",
                choice2: "Winter Soldier",
                choice3: "Spiderman",
                choice4: "Black Widow",
                answer: 3,
            },

            {
                question: "What year did the first Iron Man movie come out?",
                choice1: "2001",
                choice2: "2014",
                choice3: "2010",
                choice4: "2008",
                answer: 4,
            },


            {
                question: "What is Pepper Potts' superhero name??",
                choice1: "Iron Man",
                choice2: "Super Pots",
                choice3: "Rescue",
                choice4: "Aqua Woman",
                answer: 3,
            },


            {
                question: "What’s the name of Iron Man's computer system??",
                choice1: "Monday",
                choice2: "Haris",
                choice3: "Marvin",
                choice4: "Jarvis",
                answer: 4,
            },


            {
                question: "What is the name of the actor who plays Iron Man?",
                choice1: "Iron Man",
                choice2: "Robert Downey Jr",
                choice3: "Captain America",
                choice4: "hulk",
                answer: 2,
            },


            {
                question: "Who was the villain of Iron Man 3?",
                choice1: "The Dark Elves",
                choice2: "The Mandarin",
                choice3: "The Mandalorian",
                choice4: "The Silver Surfer",
                answer: 2,
            },


            {
                question: "Who did Iron Man face off against in Civil War? ",
                choice1: "Howard Stark",
                choice2: "Batman",
                choice3: "Captain America",
                choice4: "Hulk",
                answer: 3,
            },


            {
                question: "What's the name of the device in Tony's chest?",
                choice1: "Silver Heart",
                choice2: "Curve Reactor",
                choice3: "The Force",
                choice4: "Arc Reactor",
                answer: 4,
            },


            {
                question: "Who was Stark kidnapped by in Iron Man 1?",
                choice1: "The 10 Rings",
                choice2: "Nick Fury",
                choice3: "The Wakondians",
                choice4: "Iron Mongler",
                answer: 1,
            },


            {
                question: "How did Tony's parents supposable die?",
                choice1: "Plane Crash",
                choice2: "Sailing",
                choice3: "Car Crash",
                choice4: "Storm",
                answer: 3,
            },

            {
                question: "What was the super-name of Obidiah Stane?",
                choice1: "Hawk Eye",
                choice2: "Thor",
                choice3: "Iron Mongler",
                choice4: "Loki",
                answer: 3,
            },
            
            {
                question: "What was the name of the peacekeeping AI Stark built?",
                choice1: "P.E.A.C.E.",
                choice2: "Veltron",
                choice3: "Iron Shield",
                choice4: "Ultron",
                answer: 4,
            },

            {
                question: "How did Tony's parents supposable die?",
                choice1: "Plane Crash",
                choice2: "Sailing",
                choice3: "Car Crash",
                choice4: "Storm",
                answer: 3,
            },

            {
                question: "What job does Happy Hogan do for Tony?",
                choice1: "Butler",
                choice2: "SideKick",
                choice3: "Body Gaurd",
                choice4: "Chauffeur",
                answer: 4,
            },

            {
                question: "What super-team is Iron Man a founding member of?",
                choice1: "Iron Legion",
                choice2: "Avengers",
                choice3: "Team Titan",
                choice4: "Gaurdians of the Galaxy",
                answer: 2,
            },

            {
                question: "What's Tony Stark's address?",
                choice1: "Stark Industries",
                choice2: "Asgaurd",
                choice3: "10880 Malibu Point",
                choice4: "New York",
                answer: 3,
            },

            {
                question: "What is the name of the suit Tony makes for Spider-Man?",
                choice1: "Iron Spider",
                choice2: "Silk Web",
                choice3: "Spider Suit Mk2",
                choice4: "Spidey Suit 2",
                answer: 1,
            },

            {
                question: "Who created the character of Iron Man? ",
                choice1: "Stan Lee",
                choice2: "Robert Lin",
                choice3: "Stan Herbert",
                choice4: "Stan W.S.",
                answer: 1,
            },

            {
                question: "What's the name of Tony Stark's father?",
                choice1: "Tom",
                choice2: "Harry",
                choice3: "Francis",
                choice4: "Howard",
                answer: 4,
            },

            {
                question: "Which college did Tony Stark go to?",
                choice1: "Code Institute",
                choice2: "Harverd",
                choice3: "M.I.T.",
                choice4: "Yale",
                answer: 3,
            },

            {
                question: "In which city is the F1 race that Tony takes part in?",
                choice1: "Dublin",
                choice2: "Paris",
                choice3: "New York",
                choice4: "Monico",
                answer: 4,
            },

            {
                question: "What Character killed Tony Starks Parents.?",
                choice1: "Captain America",
                choice2: "Winter Soldier",
                choice3: "Thor",
                choice4: "Iron Man",
                answer: 2,
            },

            {
                question: "Tony starks father created what Famous weapon.?",
                choice1: "Captain America Shield",
                choice2: "Iron Man",
                choice3: "Twin Pulse lasers",
                choice4: "Hulk Buster",
                answer: 1,
            },

            {
                question: "Whats the name of the suit tony used to fight the Hulk.?",
                choice1: "Ultron",
                choice2: "Hulk Buster",
                choice3: "Jarvis",
                choice4: "Rescue",
                answer: 2,
            },


                 

                 



     
 ]